http://www.woodheatstoves.com/pages/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, storage, sharing and protection of your personal information. It applies to the Wood Heat Stoves website and all related sites, applications, services and tools regardless of how you access or use them. More detailed information about our privacy practices and our contact information for any questions is available. You accept this Privacy Policy when you sign up for, access, or use our products, services, content, features, technologies or functions offered on our website and all related sites, applications, and services (collectively Wood Heat Stoves services). We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. How we collect information about you:When you visit the Wood Heat Stoves website, we collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone or other access device. The information sent to us includes data on the pages you access, your computer IP address, device identifiers, the type of operating system you’re using, your location, mobile network information, standard web log data and other information. Web log data includes the browser type you’re using and traffic to and from our site. When you visit the Wood Heat Stoves website we also collect information about your transactions and your activities.We may collect the following types of information:· Contact information, such as your name, address, phone, email, and other similar information.· Financial information, such as the full bank account numbers and/or credit card numbers that you link to your PayPal account or give us when you use PayPal Services.· Detailed personal information such as your date of birth or social security number.You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by third parties such as social media sites (e.g., Facebook and Twitter). The information we may receive varies by site and is controlled by that site. By associating an account managed by a third party with your Wood Heat Stoves account and authorizing Wood Heat Stoves to have access to this information, you agree that Wood Heat Stoves may collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.How we protect and store personal information:Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous so that it does not identify a specific user.We store and process your personal information on our computers in the US.. We protect your information using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls.How we use the personal information we collect:Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:· Provide Wood Heat Stoves service and customer support;· Process transactions and send notices about your transactions;· Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;· Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement;· Customize, measure, and improve Wood Heat Stoves Services and the content, layout, and operation of our websites and applications;· Deliver targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;· Contact you at any telephone number.Registration:In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Orders:We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address and phone number) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.Links:This web site contains links to other sites such as Facebook, YouTube, and our blogs. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. Marketing:We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes.  How we share personal information with other partiesWe may share your personal information with:· Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process or requirement applicable to Wood Heat Stoves; when we need to do so to comply with law or credit card rules; or when we believe, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations..· Other third parties with your consent or direction to do so.Wood Heat Stoves will not sell or rent any of your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes and only shares your personal information with third parties as described in this policy.How you can contact us about privacy questions:If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy or need to make changes to your information, you should contact us by email Info@Woodheatstoves.com Policy effective January 1, 2008
